Guide to the Transport Workers Union of America Records WAG.235
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series I: Files of Michael J. Quill, 1928-1970.
  - Subseries I:B: New York City Council and Other Political Files, 1935-1955.
    - Greater New York CIO Council: Political Action, 1945-1946 (Box 30, Folder 35)
    - Greater New York Industrial Union Council, 1940-1943 (Box 30, Folder 36)
    - Greek-American Labor Conference, 1943 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Harlem Legislative Conference, 1940 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Hellman, Lillian, 1938 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Henry George School of Social Science, 1938 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Hillman, Sidney: Testimony on Campaign Spending, 1944 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Housing, 1938; 1939; 1941 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Independent Citizens Committee for the Reelection of Michael J. Quill, 1945 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Independent Citizens Committee for the Reelection of Michael J. Quill: Finances (I), 1945 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Independent Citizens Committee for the Reelection of Michael J. Quill: Finances (II), 1945 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Independent Hackmen of New York, 1938 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - International Communist Labor Committee, 1945 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Irish-American Committee for the Election of O'Dwyer and Quill, 1945 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Irish American History: Quill Speech, 1939 (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - Isacson, Leo: Campaign, 1944 (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Isacson, Leo: Campaign, 1946 (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - Isacson, Leo: Campaign (Congressional), 1948 (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - Japanese-American Committee for Democracy, 1943 (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - Jewish People's Committee on Anti-Semitism, 1943 (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - Joint Anti-Fascist Refugee Committee, 1943; 1946 (Box 31, Folder 19)
    - Junior Town Crier (Bronx House Newsletter): Anti-Nazi Issue, 1938 (Box 31, Folder 20)
    - Ku Klux Klan: Quill Resolution, 1947 (Box 31, Folder 21)
    - Labor's Non-Partisan League, 1939 (Box 31, Folder 22)
    - LaGuardia, Mayor Fiorello, 1938; 1939 (Box 31, Folder 23)
    - League of Women Voters, 1939 (Box 31, Folder 24)
    - Lease: 2488 Grand Concourse, Bronx, 1947 (Box 31, Folder 25)
    - Legislative Analysis and Index, 1938 (Box 31, Folder 26)
    - Legislators List: NYC, Undated (Box 31, Folder 27)
    - Lincoln Hospital Malpractice Issue, 1939 (Box 31, Folder 28)
    - Local Laws, Proposals and Memoranda, 1938 (Box 31, Folder 29)
    - Local Laws, Proposals and Memoranda, 1939 (Box 31, Folder 30)
    - Lower Bronx Social Welfare League, 1938 (Box 31, Folder 31)
    - Manuals, Rules of the New York City Council, 1938-1939 (Box 31, Folder 32)
    - Marcantonio, Vito, Undated; 1941 (Box 31, Folder 33)
    - Marcantonio, Vito: Campaign, 1941 (Box 31, Folder 34)
    - Marcantonio, Vito: Campaign, 1946 (Box 31, Folder 35)
    - Minority Leader's Office, 1939; 1944 (Box 31, Folder 36)
    - Monopolies and Trusts, 1946 (Box 31, Folder 37)
    - Morris, Newbold, Undated (Box 31, Folder 38)
    - Municipal Power Plant, 1939 (Box 31, Folder 39)
    - NAACP, 1944 (Box 31, Folder 40)
    - National Council of American-Soviet Friendship, 1943 (Box 31, Folder 41)
    - National Negro Conference, 1943; 1946 (Box 31, Folder 42)
    - National Urban League, 1946 (Box 31, Folder 43)
    - National Youth Administration, 1939 (Box 31, Folder 44)
    - New York City Board of Elections: Annual Report, 1943 (Box 31, Folder 45)
    - New York City Budget, 1944 (Box 31, Folder 46)
    - New York City Budget, 1945 (Box 31, Folder 47)
    - New York City Council: Annual Outing, Undated (Box 31, Folder 48)
    - New York City Council: Qualifications for Membership, 1938; Undated (Box 31, Folder 49)
    - New York City Department of Health, 1938 (Box 31, Folder 50)
    - New York City Department of Markets, 1939 (Box 31, Folder 51)
    - New York City: Employees Union, Local 61, 1939 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - New York City: Office of the Comptroller, 1939 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - NYC Voluntary Hospitals: Wage Issue Correspondence; Press Releases: National Health Survey Bulletin; Clippings, 1937-1938 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - NYC County Clubs: List, Undated (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - New York League of Women Shoppers, 1938 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - New York State Conference on Women Workers, 1943-1944 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - New York State Industrial Union Council, 1943 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Non-Sectarian Committee for German Refugee Children, 1939 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Notes: Miscellaneous, Undated (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - O'Donnell, John, 1938 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - O'Dwyer, William: Campaigns, 1938; 1945 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - O'Reilly, Gerald: Campaign, 1946 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - O'Reilly, Gerald: Fordham American Labor Party Club, etc., 1943-1947 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - O'Riordan, Michael: Letter to William Gandall (Fellow Spanish Civil War Veteran), 1939 (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Palestine: Quill Statement, 1945 (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - Parkchester: Rent Problems, 1947 (Box 32, Folder 16)
    - Pending Bills, 1944-1945 (Box 32, Folder 17)
    - People's Voice: "Help Organize the South" Conference, 1945 (Box 32, Folder 18)
    - Platform (Quill), 1943 (Box 32, Folder 19)
    - Police, Undated (Box 32, Folder 20)
    - Police Pass (MJQ), 1949 (Box 32, Folder 21)
    - Powell, Adam Clayton, Jr., Undated (Box 32, Folder 22)
    - Press Releases, 1944-1946 (Box 32, Folder 23)
    - Press Releases, 1947-1948 (Box 32, Folder 24)
    - Price Controls, 1944 (Box 32, Folder 25)
    - Public Dental Care, 1938 (Box 32, Folder 26)
    - Public School 39 (Bronx), Parents Association: Quill Speech on Housing, 1939 (Box 32, Folder 27)
    - Quill Association, 1944 (Box 32, Folder 28)
    - Quill Association: Correspondence, 1941-1945 (Box 32, Folder 29)
    - Quill Association: First Annual Ball, 1944-1945 (Box 32, Folder 30)
    - Quill Association: First Annual Dinner Meeting, Nov-Dec 1944 (Box 32, Folder 31)
    - Quill Association: Membership, 1944 (Box 32, Folder 32)
    - Quill Association: Membership, 1945-1946 (Box 32, Folder 33)
    - Quill Association: Publicity, 1943-1945 (Box 32, Folder 34)
    - Quill Council Record, 1944-1945 (Box 32, Folder 35)
    - Quill Testimonial, 1947 (Box 32, Folder 36)
    - Quill Testimonial: Bills, 1947 (Box 32, Folder 37)
    - Quill Testimonial: Journal, 1939; 1945-1947 (Box 32, Folder 38)
    - Racial Issues, Undated; 1939 (Box 32, Folder 39)
    - Rent Cases, 1947-1948 (Box 32, Folder 40)
    - Rent Case: Breslin Conviction, 1947-1948 (Box 32, Folder 41)
    - Rent Case: C, 1948 (Box 32, Folder 42)
    - Rent Case: D, 1948 (Box 32, Folder 43)
    - Rent Case: E, 1948 (Box 32, Folder 44)
    - Rent Case: F, 1948 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Rent Case: G, 1947-1948 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Rent Cases: H, 1948 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Rent Service, 1944 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Resolution #4: Cigarette, Utility Tax, 1944 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Resolution #6: Investigation of Power Companies, 1946 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Resolution #18: Fiscal Needs, 1946 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Resolution #19: Transit Collective Bargaining, 1938 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Resolution #21: Amendment of Disability Retirement Rules, 1940 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Resolution #26: Discrimination on CUNY, 1946 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Resolution #27: Withdrawal of Tax Exemptions, 1946 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Resolution #28, 79: State Bonus for Veterans, 1948 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Resolution #30: Unemployment for Strikers, 1948 (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Resolution #31: Pension Contributions, 1946 (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - Resolution #55: Civil Service Seniority, 1946 (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - Resolution #56: Minimum Wage for Cops and Firefighters, 1946 (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - Resolution #57: Working Conditions in FDNY, 1945 (Box 33, Folder 17)
    - Resolution #91: Construction of Cross-Bronx Expressway, 1946 (Box 33, Folder 18)
    - Resolution #92: Firefighters' Grievances, 1944 (Box 33, Folder 19)
    - Resolution #102: 10% Rent Increase, 1944 (Box 33, Folder 20)
    - Resolution #103: Wage Increase for Postal Workers, 1944 (Box 33, Folder 21)
    - Resolution #107: Commercial Rent Control, 1944 (Box 33, Folder 22)
    - Resolution #108: Pay Increases for Federal Workers, 1944 (Box 33, Folder 23)
    - Resolution #118: Qualifying Exams for Temporary Firemen, 1946 (Box 33, Folder 24)
    - Resolution #119: School Facilities of Hunter College, Undated (Box 33, Folder 25)
    - Resolution #120: Housing for Veterans, 1946 (Box 33, Folder 26)
    - Resolution #121: Transit Workers Pay, 1944 (Box 33, Folder 27)
    - Resolution #125: "Meat Holiday", 1944 (Box 33, Folder 28)
    - Resolution #127: Problems in Taxicab Industry, 1944 (Box 33, Folder 29)
    - Resolution #128: Discrimination at Columbia University, 1946 (Box 33, Folder 30)
    - Resolution #164: Disability Retirement, 1945 (Box 33, Folder 31)
    - Resolution #105: Retirement Deductions, 1945 (Box 33, Folder 32)
    - Resolution #173: Major Deegan Highway, 1947 (Box 33, Folder 33)
    - Resolution #180: Violations of Rationing Regulations, 1945 (Box 33, Folder 34)
    - Resolution #181: Fraudulent Sales of Merchandise, 1945 (Box 33, Folder 35)
    - Resolution #182: Pension Transfer, 1945 (Box 33, Folder 36)
    - Resolution #196: Hate Mail, 1945 (Box 33, Folder 37)
    - Resolution #197: New Taxis, 1945 (Box 33, Folder 38)
    - Resolution #205: Lend-Lease to Italy, 1945 (Box 33, Folder 39)
    - Resolution #206: Merchant Marine, 1945 (Box 33, Folder 40)
    - Resolution #212: Increases in Welfare Allowance, 1946-1947 (Box 33, Folder 41)
    - Resolution #219: Housing Shortage, 1945 (Box 33, Folder 42)
    - Resolution #220: Wages and Working Conditions for Postal Workers, 1945 (Box 33, Folder 43)
    - Resolution #222: Re-conversion of Plants, 1945 (Box 33, Folder 44)
    - Resolution #223: Full Employment, 1945 (Box 33, Folder 45)
    - Resolution #233: Federal Labor Relations Administration, 1945 (Box 33, Folder 46)
    - Resolution #234: Condemnation of Governor Bilbo of Mississippi, 1945 (Box 33, Folder 47)
    - Resolution #250: Investigation of Anti-Semitic Disturbances, 1945 (Box 33, Folder 48)
    - Resolution #271: Traffic Lights in Parkchester, 1946-1947 (Box 33, Folder 49)
    - Resolution #275: Investigation into Tenement Fire at 2515 Amsterdam Ave., 1946 (Box 33, Folder 50)
    - Resolution #276: Relief Funds of Victims of Fire at 2515 Amsterdam Ave., 1946 (Box 33, Folder 51)
    - Resolution #281: Funding For B52, BX, Destroyed by Fire, 1946-1947 (Box 33, Folder 52)
    - Resolution #288: Additional Paid Holidays for Sanitation Men, 1946 (Box 33, Folder 53)
    - Resolution #297: Blocking Mass Eviction from Public Housing, 1947 (Box 33, Folder 54)
    - Resolution #303: Pensions for Civil Servants Who Are Veterans, 1947 (Box 33, Folder 55)
    - Resolution #304: Retirement of Accidentally Disabled City Employees, 1947 (Box 33, Folder 56)
    - Resolution #329: Irving Trust and Union Busting, 1947 (Box 33, Folder 57)
    - Resolution #330: Publication of KKK Membership List, 1947 (Box 33, Folder 58)
    - Resolution #344: Condemning Use of Book "Lanterns on the Levee" in Public Schools, 1947 (Box 33, Folder 59)
    - Resolution #345: Condemning Use of Book "How To Create Cartoons" in Public School System, 1947 (Box 33, Folder 60)
    - Resolution #346: Investigation of Books Used in Public School System Which Foster Race and Religious Prejudice, 1947 (Box 33, Folder 61)
    - Resolution #380: Urging Adoption of Unemployment Insurance for State and Local Government Employees, 1947 (Box 33, Folder 62)
    - Resolution #381: Urging Adoption of Amendments to State Residential Rent Control Law, 1947 (Box 33, Folder 63)
    - Resolution #382: Urging Adoption of Amendments to Civil Practice Act to Permit a 12-Month Stay of Eviction, 1947 (Box 33, Folder 64)
    - Resolution #384: Proposed Local Law to Require Certificate from Health Department to Permit Execution of Warrants of Eviction, 1947 (Box 33, Folder 65)
    - Resolution #391: Supporting Demands of Teachers for Salary Increases, 1947 (Box 33, Folder 66)
    - Resolution #393: Supporting Fino-Crews Bill on Retirement of City Employees for Accident Disability, 1947 (Box 33, Folder 67)
    - Resolution #395: Opposing Pending Anti-Labor Legislation in Congress (Taft-Hartley Bill), 1947 (Box 33, Folder 68)
    - Resolution #424: Urging Federal Government Not to Transfer New York Office of Veterans Administration to Washington, 1947 (Box 33, Folder 69)
    - Resolution #425: Discriminatory Hiring Practices at Bronx Internal Revenue Bureau, 1947 (Box 33, Folder 70)
    - Resolution #435: Aid for Ireland, 1947 (Box 33, Folder 71)
    - Resolution #466: Urging Enactment of Federal Law Forbidding Use of Mails for Dissemination of Racist Propaganda, 1947 (Box 33, Folder 72)
    - Resolution #477: Calling on Robert Moses to Open Empty Apartments, 1947 (Box 33, Folder 73)
    - Resolution #546: Journalistic Attacks on Puerto Ricans, 1947 (Box 33, Folder 74)
    - Resolution #567: Winter Heat, 1947 (Box 33, Folder 75)
    - Resolution #568: Installation of Traffic Light, 1947 (Box 33, Folder 76)
    - Resolution #569: Sanitation Day, 1947 (Box 33, Folder 77)
    - Resolution #570: Fair Employment, 1948 (Box 33, Folder 78)
    - Resolution #577: Burning of Pinball Machines, 1948 (Box 33, Folder 79)
    - Resolution #579: Arson Investigation, 1947-1948 (Box 33, Folder 80)
    - Resolution #581: Retention of Substitute Teachers, 1948 (Box 33, Folder 81)
    - Resolution #693: Retention of Teachers, 1948 (Box 33, Folder 82)
    - Resolution #697: UN and Israel, 1948 (Box 33, Folder 83)
    - Resolution #707: Ban on Books Gentlemen's Agreement and Focus, 1948-1949 (Box 33, Folder 84)
    - Resolution #722: Veterans Services, 1948 (Box 33, Folder 85)
    - Resolution #731, Int. 611: Pension and Retirement Computations, 1948-1949 (Box 33, Folder 86)
    - Resolution #994: Postponement of Cross-Bronx Expressway Construction, 1949 (Box 33, Folder 87)
    - Resolution #1089: Registration of City Owned Property, 1949 (Box 33, Folder 88)
    - Resolution #1008: Reinstatement of Civil Employees, 1949 (Box 33, Folder 89)
    - Resolution #1090: Tax Exemption for Disability Pensions, 1949 (Box 33, Folder 90)
    - Resolution #1091: Group Libel Bill, 1949 (Box 33, Folder 91)
    - Resolution #1133: Playgrounds, Undated (Box 33, Folder 92)
    - Resolution #1134: Enlargement and Improvement of Corona Park, Undated (Box 33, Folder 93)
    - Resolution: Limiting Freedom of Nominations, Undated (Box 33, Folder 94)
    - Resolution: Transit Labor, 1938 (Box 33, Folder 95)
    - Resolution: Transit (vs. Wicks Bill), 1939 (Box 33, Folder 96)
    - Resolution: Inclusion of Merchant Marine in Military Law, 1944 (Box 33, Folder 97)
    - Resolution: Taxi Regulation, 1944 (Box 33, Folder 98)
    - Resolution: "Fight Inflation Week", 1945 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Resolution: Truman and Labor, 1946 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Resolution: Parking Privileges for the Disabled and Amputees, 1947 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Resolution: Accidental Disability, 1948 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Resolution: Disabled Veterans' Eligibility for Public Housing, 1948 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Resolution: Extension of Rent Control, 1948 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Resolution: Investigation of Eastside Comprehensive Bus Company, 1948 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Resolution: Killing of Jewish Boys in Palestine, 1948 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Resolution: Playground Construction, 1948 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Resolution: Psychiatric Services Staff Salaries, 1946-1949 (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Resolution: Recognizing the State of Israel, 1948 (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - Resolution: Reinstatement of Books to School Library, 1948 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Resolution: Requiring Landlords to Provide Adequate Heat, Water, Plumbing, 1948-1949 (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - Resolution: Adequate Heating in Veterans' Emergency Projects, 1949 (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - Resolution: Construction of PS 109, Bronx, 1949 (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - Resolution: Fire Code Building Practices, 1949 (Box 34, Folder 16)
    - Resolution: Health and Fire Hazards in Tenements, 1949 (Box 34, Folder 17)
    - Resolution: Infiltration, 1949 (Box 34, Folder 18)
    - Resolution: Problems with Welfare Department Rules and Regulations, 1949 (Box 34, Folder 19)
    - Resolution: Telegraph Service, 1949 (Box 34, Folder 20)
    - Resolution: Clippings, 1944-1949 (Box 34, Folder 21)
    - Resolutions: Miscellaneous, Undated (Box 34, Folder 22)
    - Resolutions: Miscellaneous, 1938-1949 (Box 34, Folder 23)
    - Robeson, Paul, 1945-1946 (Box 34, Folder 24)
    - Rodney, George H.: Campaign, 1946 (Box 34, Folder 25)
    - Roosevelt, Eleanor, 1944 (Box 34, Folder 26)
    - Sales Tax, 1946 (Box 34, Folder 27)
    - San Francisco: Quill Appearances, 1941; 1944 (Box 34, Folder 28)
    - Sanitation, 1939 (Box 34, Folder 29)
    - Save Czechoslovakia Committee, 1938 (Box 34, Folder 30)
    - Schappes Defense Committee, 1943; Undated (Box 34, Folder 31)
    - Schorr, Daniel L., 1939 (Box 34, Folder 32)
    - Sharkey Housing Amendment, 1946 (Box 34, Folder 33)
    - Sheepshead Bay Town News, 1945 (Box 34, Folder 34)
    - Sleepy Lagoon Defense Committee, 1944 (Box 34, Folder 35)
    - Socialist Party/Norman Thomas: Request for Anti-Communist Statement and Quill Reply, 1939 (Box 34, Folder 36)
    - South Bronx Citizens Association, Undated (Box 34, Folder 37)
    - Southern Negro Youth Congress, 1946 (Box 34, Folder 38)
    - Spanish Civil War, 1939 (Box 34, Folder 39)
    - Speaking Engagements, 1946-1948 (Box 34, Folder 40)
    - State, County, and Municipal Workers Association, Local 40: The Union Counselor, Mar., 1939 (Box 34, Folder 41)
    - State, County, and Municipal Workers of America, Local 1: Welfare Conference, 1946 (Box 34, Folder 42)
    - Steel, Johannes: Campaign, 1946 (Box 34, Folder 43)
    - Taxpayers Associations: Mass Meeting, 1939 (Box 34, Folder 44)
    - Teachers Union, Undated, 1939 (Box 34, Folder 45)
    - Teachers Union: May Quinn Case, 1945 (Box 34, Folder 46)
    - Trade Union Conference: Registration Forms, 1939 (Box 34, Folder 47)
    - Transit Workers Committee of 1000 for O'Dwyer and Quill, 1945 (Box 34, Folder 48)
    - Typographical Union Number 6, 1938 (Box 34, Folder 49)
    - Unemployment, 1939 (Box 34, Folder 50)
    - United Negro, 1946 (Box 34, Folder 51)
    - United Rubber Workers of America, Local 830, 1939 (Box 34, Folder 52)
    - Veterans Housing Council: Fuel Oil Crisis, 1948 (Box 34, Folder 53)
    - Voter Registration, 1940 (Box 34, Folder 54)
    - Voter Registration (Including Problems), 1943-1946 (Box 34, Folder 55)
    - War Finance Committee for New York, 1944 (Box 34, Folder 56)
    - Washington Industrial Union Council: Quill Speech, 1940 (Box 34, Folder 57)
    - Welfare Council of New York City: Conferences, 1942; 1945 (Box 34, Folder 58)
    - Westchester Independent Political Club, 1937 (Box 34, Folder 59)
    - West Side Child Care Council, 1943 (Box 34, Folder 60)
    - West Side Defense Council: Armistice Day Conference, Undated (Box 34, Folder 61)
    - "Win the Peace" Conference, 1946 (Box 34, Folder 62)
    - Works Progress Administration, 1939 (Box 34, Folder 63)
- Series II: Files of Matthew Guinan, 1935-1978.
  Subseries I:B: New York City Council Files, 1937-1948, provides a detailed record of Mike Quill's political activity, beginning with his successful 1937 campaign, on the American Labor Party (ALP) ticket, for a seat on the New York City Council representing a district in the Bronx. Flyers, brochures, reports, correspondence, financial records and voter lists from this and his subsequent Council campaigns, and accompanied by material documenting the campaigns of other ALP and ALP-endorsed candidates (notably Congressmen Vito Marcantonio and Leo Isaacson, and Mayor William O'Dwyer). Also included are files of material illustrating Quill's appeals to various ethnic groups (in many languages), letters of support from other CIO unions, documentation of CIO political activity in New York City, and the records of support groups such as the Quill Association, the Independent Citizens Committee to Elect Quill, the TWU's Committee to Elect Quill and various neighborhood groups. Correspondence files and files of bills and resolutions introduced or supported by Quill reflect the range of his political concerns (including housing, health care, working conditions of public employees, immigrant affairs, price controls and other consumer issues and anti-discrimination measures).
  - A. Philip Randolph Institute, 1974 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Administrative Committee, 1959-1960 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Administrative Committee, 1961 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Administrative Committee, 1962-1963 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Administrative Committee, 1964-1965 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Administrative Committee, 1966 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - African Students, 1961-1963 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Agreements: Various Locals, 1962-1963 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Air Transport Division, 1959 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Air Transport Division, 1960 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Air Transport Division, 1961 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Air Transport Division, 1962 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Air Transport Division, 1963 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Air Transport Division, 1964 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Air Transport Division, 1965 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Air Transport Division, 1974-1975 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Air Transport Division: Airline Merger, 1962 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Air Transport Division: American Airlines Negotiations, 1960-1962 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Air Transport Division: Eastern Airlines Flight Engineers, 1964 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Air Transport Division: Federal Aviation Agency, 1964-1965 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Air Transport Division: Locals 504, 550 (Chicago), 1961-1967 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Air Transport Division: Local 550 (Chicago), Undated; 1964; 1966 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Air Transport Division: Pan-American Airlines, 1964-1965 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Air Transport Division: Supersonic Jet (SST), 1965 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Airriess, Leonard, 1960-1969 (Box 36, Folder 8a)
  - Amalgamated Transit Union, 1964 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - American Airlines, 1956-1959 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - American Arbitration Association, 1966-1969 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - American Civil Liberties Union (ACLU), 1969 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO), 1959-1960 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - AFL-CIO, 1962 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - AFL-CIO, 1963-1965 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - AFL-CIO, 1966-1967 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - AFL-CIO, 1968-1969 (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - AFL-CIO: Civil Rights Communications, 1969 (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - AFL-CIO: Clippings, 1964-1967 (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - AFL-CIO: Committee on Political Education (COPE), 1959 (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - AFL-CIO: COPE, 1968-1969 (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - AFL-CIO: COPE, 1970-1971 (Box 36, Folder 22)
  - AFL-CIO: COPE (Al Barkan), 1969 (Box 36, Folder 23)
  - AFL-CIO: COPE (Ernest Mitchell), 1969 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - AFL-CIO: Community Services Institute, 1963-1967 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - AFL-CIO: Community Services Institute, 1968-1969 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - AFL-CIO: Convention, 1961 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - AFL-CIO: Convention, 1963 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - AFL-CIO: Convention, 1969 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - AFL-CIO: Ethical Practices Committee, 1960 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - AFL-CIO: Executive Council, 1961-1963 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - AFL-CIO: Executive Council, 1959 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - AFL-CIO: Executive Council, 1960 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - AFL-CIO: Executive Council, 1967 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - AFL-CIO: Executive Council, 1969-1970 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - AFL-CIO: General Board, 1964-1967 (Box 37, Folder 13)